SARAH BARBER

PERSPECTIVE INTERN



+1 (336) 875-1798



Smbarber2@uncg.edu



1010 Kildare Rd, Asheboro, NC, 27203



https://www.linkedin.co m/in/sarah-barber-108343233

OBJECTIVE

I am a computer science student interested in getting hands-on experience before graduating. I currently work at the Esports Gaming Arena on campus, so I have a lot of experience with tech support, team management, and customer service, but I'd like to find an internship that can offer me work more focused on computer science itself. I recently spent a semester studying abroad in Nagoya, Japan, so I have experience navigating a new culture and dealing with any problems that may arise due to that.

EXPERIENCE

April 2022 - Present

Esports Arena Supervisor • UNCG: Recreation and Wellness

- Set up and performed upkeep on a range of different electronics, such as PCs, gaming consoles, and Shoutcasting equipment.
- Assisted in the running of engagement events and programs for students within the arena.

October 2020 - Present

Seasonal Poll Worker • Randolph County Board of Elections

• Monitored members of the public for compliance with security measures and other procedures.

August 2019 - September 2019

Administrative Assistant • Sedgwick

- Established a record filing system to improve document organization and management.
- Filled, labeled, and prepared packages for shipment.

June 2018 - August 2019

Maker Mentor • Summer Camp Counselor • UNCG

- Implemented STEM based camp activities focusing on physical, social, and emotional growth.
- Organized and guided group activities by mentoring, helping and participating with campers.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Greensboro, NC

- 3.7 GPA
- COMPUTER SCIENCE MAJOR
- ENGLISH MINOR
- MEMBER OF THE LLOYD
 INTERNATIONAL HONORS
 COLLEGE
- STUDIED ABROAD IN JAPAN
 AT NAGOYA UNIVERSITY FOR
 FOREIGN STUDY

KEY SKILLS

- NATIVE SPANISH SPEAKER
- NOVICE JAPANESE (STUDIED ABROAD)
- CUSTOMER SERVICE
- JAVA PROGRAMMING
- HTML PROGRAMMING
- PROGRAM MANAGEMENT
- TECH SUPPORT

LEADERSHIP

I am currently the president and founder of the UNCG Game Development Coalition on campus, a project dedicated to the unification of different departments on campus to bring students together to create video games. Our goal is to strengthen the bonds between students and let students put their skills to use in the form of video game development.

REFERENCES

Matthew Fisher, Former Colleague

Email: msfishe2@uncg.edu

Mike Ackerman, Current Employer Email: maacker2@uncg.edu

AWARDS

- EMPLOYEE OF THE YEAR 2023
- RECIPIENT OF THE CHANCELLOR'S SCHOLARSHIP